It's amazing the people you don't get to meet unless you sell.
I heard he was amazing.
Hirate Yorinosan
Ah, Hirate-san.
For example, Ken Hirai and Nonfiction at FNS
I asked him to collaborate with me.
And from then on...
Wow, that's great
This is...
There's only one Bob, so I think it's a bit of a waste to bring in a blonde.
I feel like it could have been a little more appropriate.
I don't know why we're doing this project today.
I really don't know about this one.
Hi, I'm Tokyo Dyson. Please do me a favor.
Kattara and Sakuma, please.
And here they are again today.
Funny, funny, funny.
What's up?
Where do you want to start?
You're saying funny, funny, funny, but you're not sure if you're really allowed to say that, are you?
You're not sure?
Are you confused?
It's okay.
Funny, funny, funny, everybody's funny.
We can do comedy.
We got it.
Ready?
Ruff Ruff.
Please.
We made it through the run. Good.
This time, we're going to do a project.
This is another very popular project.
Let's get people in the industry to remember us.
Mr. Sakuma, this time?
No, this time it's great.
Where did you come from?From where?
From Fuji Television in Odaiba.
I'm the director of a music program.
I'm directing the FNS Tuesday Festival.
Wow, that's great.
I'm also the director of All Night Fuji Television.
I'm working on it now.
I'm the chief director of that.
So you know him well?
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, let's have him appear.
This way, please.
Please.
Pleased to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
You're very modest, aren't you?
So, our guest this time is...
Fuji Television's music program director.
Kazumasa Shimada, director of Fuji Television's music program.
Pleased to meet you.
I look forward to working with you.
Please review.
Pleased to meet you.
You've been with Fuji Television for 16 years.
You've been in charge of music programs?
Yes, I've been doing it for 16 years.
Music Fair, FNS Tuesday Festival.
And Rough & Music?
I did Rough & Music.
I see.
And if I don't do it, you'll do Fujiko too.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
And I'm sure you'll all be in good hands.
That's why we met here.
But if I meet Shimada-kun at work it means I've sold it.
That's true.Oh, you're right.
It's important to meet people on the spot.
You have to be successful to meet him.
Someone you can't meet unless you sell.
So, Shimada-san...
Shimada-san has something he wants to say to Sakuma-san.
I wonder...
You've known me for years, right, Sakuma-san?
I know you.
And you too, Fujiko.
Why don't you follow me on Twitter?
He framed it like a middle-schooler.
What's this for, Mr. Sakuma?
No, no, no...
It's not just about following me on Twitter.
It's not only because I'm a private person.
I'm basically in a relationship with people in the industry
I mean...
I followed you on Twitter once... once.
What about you, Shimada-san?
Really?
But Shimada-kun...
He's a total idol nerd.
I see.
He's amazing.
Really.
He sends out messages to all kinds of idols.
I can see it.
It's amazing.
I've got a hub.
It took me about a day to do it.
So you're following her once.
I see.
I got Shimada-san's T-shirt today.
Ruff Ruff merchandise.A Little Rough Ruff Ruff Goods.
A little bit of Ruff Ruff's goodies.
So that means...
You're here to see it, right?
That's right.
I went to the big show, too.
The pond before that.
Sunshine.
Oh!
I'm here to see it.
I came to see you.
Did you know I was here?
Yes, I knew.
I'm going to have to charm you.
That's a bit...
I've been to most of the sites.
I've been going around a lot.
And see all kinds of things
and see for yourself.
That's why I invited Shimada-san this time.
Sakuma-san
Well...
First of all, of course, he's an excellent music director.
But he's also a fan of idols.
Directors who are more like idol geeks...
Don't get this high up the ladder.
They don't get that high up.
They don't go that high.
That's why I understand how fans feel.
And I know how directors feel.
I think there's a lot that idols can learn
I think there's a lot you can learn from them.
Who was the first idol you fell in love with?
That's...
Momokuro.
Momokuro?Are you Momoguro?
She's going to visit a TV show called "Momoguro-chan
"Momoguro-chan.
I was just a fan.
Once I forgot about Fuji TV.
That's why you're watching it like that.
I was one of them
I was one of the people watching.
That's great.
Then he said he was in love with me.
Like, "Who do you like?
Who's your favorite?
That's a scary question.
She said, "Renee," and I said, "Lenny.
I didn't even get permission.
A guy from Fuji Television went all out.
I've been working with a lot of idols in my life.
You've worked with a lot of idols in the past.
You've worked with a lot of idols, right?
Did you work with any of them?
Did you work with anyone like that?
There are a lot of people.
But if you ask me who...
Yurina Hirate.
Oh, Hirate-san.
What do you like about her?
She's really stoic.
She's a performer, but she also has a behind-the-scenes perspective.
She also has a behind-the-scenes perspective.
So...
For example, I'd like you to collaborate with Ken Hirai on FNS
I asked him to collaborate with Ken Hirai
I asked him to collaborate with me.
And from there to the show
I had to hold back the tori-hashitsu for a week or 10 days.
I had to hold back the tori-hashitsu for a week or 10 days.Keep the bird hashitsu down all the time
I'll practice all the time.
Is that right?
And while you're doing that...
I want to wear this kind of costume, in this kind of space, with this kind of lighting.
In this kind of space with this kind of lighting.
with the choreographer
with the choreographer.
There are a lot of people who direct concerts
There are a lot of people who direct concerts for Japanese idols.
But not many female idols?
Not many.
I see.
I've volunteered with Hirate-san.
I volunteered with you once.
I teach at the Miller School in Fukushima.
It's a scorching summer.
I went to teach them about laughter.
And Hirate-san...
With the graduates.
I'm going to choreograph and dance the graduation dance.
There are middle and high school students, right?
And it's scorching hot.
It's a gymnasium, so there's no air conditioning.
But they're all dressed up in zelkova.
They're wearing solid zelkova outfits.
Isn't it too hot? Shouldn't you take it off?
I said.
But this is what they came here to see.
You didn't lose it in front of the kids until the end.
That's great.
You're a pro.
From your point of view, Mr. Shimada.
Did you have any suggestions about what we should do differently in the riffraff?
Or something that's missing?
Anything missing?Do you have any?
Idol groups have their own colors, don't they?
That's what we're looking for.
Group in a short distance x
Something
Equal to an individual
I thought it would be great if the distance between the group and the individual could be short, like the E-GIRLS Blonde Ami.
Like E-GIRLS Blonde Ami, for example.
It's really like that
You can tell by the zelkova costume
Instantaneously
Something that gets to the individual.
Like, for example, Mr. Takanashi, who is very hot and spicy
by the time you get to know the super-hot
there is a stroke.
But
you'd be Mr. Ruff Ruff Aunt Natsume.
That is, for example
If you go out to Tanaka and have that image
Natsume didn't seem satisfied.
She did look worried.
I'm sorry.
Shimada-san's kindness comes out.
I see.
What's this?
I just took a quick look.
This is like me.
Yoshimura.
Mr. Yoshimura.
Gumi.
I have to get to know Gumi.
There are strokes to get to know Gumi.
Tanaka
You're the shortest guy in the riffraff?
Ah...
Hayashi and YoshimuraHayashi and Yoshimura
You don't like either of them, do you?
Just try standing up.
Which is smaller?
Hayashi's is bigger.
I'm 5'9".
Yoshimura is...
153 cm.
You should put that in the back.
I think it's better to put it in the back.
I think it's fine as long as it's as tall as you are.
Like Minimoni.
What do you think? What about the blonde hair?
Is that possible?
Well, what do you think? No, but...
I'm not gonna stop you if you want to do it.
You've been saying that for a while.
I like blondes with bobs.
I used to be...
Of all the people alive today.
You're the one with the flatbed.
The word Ellery is stupid.
Since there's only one bob
If you take it all the way to blonde
I think it's a bit of a waste
So I think it would be better if someone else had blonde hair.
image of a blonde.
If I were to do it in the new Honda's way...
I wonder who it would be.
I think it's too much.
It's very difficult.
That's difficult.
I think the bottom one looks good.
Mr. Fujisaki?Mr. Fujisaki, is it?
Ooh.
You want to dye your hair, but...
You want to dye it?
I want to bleach it.
That's how much I want it... so I can't walk around with my face up.
No swelling in the chest.
You don't get swollen breasts in your hometown?
You don't get swollen breasts in your hometown.
Anybody want to change their hair?
A lot of people do.
Can't they do that without a permit?
Do you have to get a permit to do that?
No, but it's my job.
I have to take out an usher or something.
So there's that.
So that's it.
But there's no group rule
It's not a group rule that you have to have dark hair.
I see.
So it's not.
Here's a question: what was the reason for using Ms. Wakatsuki, who was a member of Nogizaka 4 6 at the time, as the main performer in the 100 idols medley at the 2015 FNS Music Festival?
Now, then, you understand. Yes, Natsume.
Because he was a push member.
I'll hit it right away.
Correct.
Just a little more.
No, that's why I thought only idiots could guess.
No way. It has a proper sense of direction. There should be more of an intention, shouldn't there?
Not at all.
It was a simple push-men.
Reni-chan and I are singing side by side.
Because the other member was also a push-men.
Wow, that's amazing.
How did you explain this? To the people around us.
There were 100 people in the group, including various AKBs, Nogizaka, Dimeguro, Ebichu, etc., and when 16 of us were asked to sing a snake song for the first song, three of Nogizaka and two or three of Wakatsuki were added, so it was a little hard to explain to them.There are 100 people in the group, so when there are various AKBs, Nogizaka, Oomeguro, Ebichu, etc., and 16 people decide to do a snake rota as the first song, we put Wakatsuki-san in two or three of the three Nogizaka members, so this is a bit hard to explain.
That's right. Because you are not in the so-called "sub-group," right?
They can't explain it to you, so they are going to tell me directly.
They would say, "Why me?
So here we are, in front of everyone, and Mr. Wakatsuki is in there because he is a push member.
Wow. Wow.
But if you put Ms. Wakatsuki in the center, it will bring out something, right?
Of course, I want to convey the goodness of the group.
I want people to know about it.
That's right.
What made you decide to push Ms. Wakatsuki and Ms. Reni Takagi?
Because Reni-chan was really kind to me.
Wakatsuki-san, I filmed Nogizaka several times for the Music Fair, and there were 16 or 18 members, so the whole room would get into a flurry of excitement.
After all the filming was over, they would playback the whole show and say, "Thank you very much for your hard work.
At that time, they would come out after cleaning up the room.
As an otaku in the industry, I made up my mind to support these girls because I wanted them to sell well.
What? If she cleaned up her room at the end, can she sing at the center of FNS?
Not at the center.
But that's not all.
I'm not the center even then.
How did you feel when you saw this snario? I knew it.
It was great.
That's right.
That's what Aisu is talking about now.
So, you know, it would be nice if I could get Shimada-san hooked or something,
But if you don't work with the intention of making everyone involved fall in love with you, you won't be able to take advantage of opportunities like this.
That's what I mean.
That's how they are looking at you, too.
By the way, do you have a boyfriend among the lovebirds?
I'm Hioki, and you're Natsume.
Oh, I see.
You wished me happy birthday in your birthday tweet, didn't you?
That's embarrassing.
That's what a reply means.
Now, let's continue. I've heard a lot about how much you like idols,
I would like to do a project that Shimada-san brought in.I would like to do a project brought in by Shimada-san.
This one is from the Laflee Squad that has been supporting Laflee,
I would like to ask you to send us your messages that you have received from your fans,
Shimada-san would like to know what kind of messages you received from fans and what kind of messages you found interesting.
Wow.
Why do you want to know?
Because I also reply to them.
Hahahahaha!
Hey, you.
Get out of here!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
This is not the time for me to be thinking about what I should be replying to.
Do you send them often?
Yes, quite often,
For example, the other day Miku Tanaka said she didn't want it, and Fujikou said he didn't want it either.
Is she cute? Like one word per picture, like "Cute? I'd reply with something like, "Cute?
Then he replied, "Please send me Fujikou.
And he replied, "Yes!
Wow!
Amazing!
Hey, guys! Give me a rip!
Give me a rip on the show you want to be in now!
You're all overdoing it.
We've asked everyone to write down a few of the people they've met in advance, so let's hear them out.
Open all at once!
Ta-da!
Yes.
Hahahahahaha!
That's funny.
What about Yoshimura?
When he told me that he forgot what he wanted to talk about when we met,
I thought to myself, I've become an idol.
Ah.
I was so happy that he was so nervous about me that he forgot what he wanted to say to me.
That surely makes the reciepients happy.
I am happy.Glad to hear it.
Nice.
Oshimada?
I feel like we've met a little more.
Hahahahaha!
Ueda-san?
Hahahahahaha!
I said that with a bit of a chuckle.
I knew there were a lot of bad guys out there.
I'm looking at them. I'm watching.
What about you, Mr. Yoshimura?
I want to live in my tear ducts.
What?
That's right.
He was happy, wasn't he?
I was happy, and I also thought it was kind of funny.
I thought he was saying this to me as a compliment.
But I thought that this kind of thing was quite common.
I think they are quite common.
I wanted to know about the ones that are really bad.
Hahahahaha!
I wanted to know them in Gendo.
What about Hayashino?
I was told that Hayashino could hit people with his bare hands.
But I thought it was funny and it left an impression on me.
It was so shocking, and it was before my debut,
I was surprised when I found it in the comments section on YouTube when I passed the audition for my debut,
I was so surprised when I found it that I reported it to my mother.
Hahahahaha!
I could have hit her.
What about this kind of thing?
Because the episode was cute.
And what about Yuka's kid?
The one with Yuka's kid.
This was done by individual members in the showroom,
It's a very small story,I'd like to talk about a very small part of it,
Do you know what Kyoto lactobacillus is?
That's it?
That's right. This place is so well developed that it is different from other people,
When I spoke sign language, this was a big hit,
Many people have come up with designs for T-shirts using the Kyoto lactobacillus.
What? Really?
But do you remember? I remember those details.
I do, and I understand how people feel when they want to say that.
I can see that I am aware of this.
Have you ever eaten something that was a little different from what you were used to?
From your point of view.
But I don't want to do that, so I don't go there. I don't want to do that, so I don't go there.
Did you change your contacts? or something like that.
I don't know! I don't know if you can go or not!
Can't you just send me a message that you're a little embarrassed by my subjectivity?
I don't know!
Shimada-san, when you go to a live concert, do you look at it from the perspective of a fan?
Or do you look at it from the perspective of a future show?
From the point of view of a fan-otaku, I guess,
Fan-otaku are industry geeks,
I go to see them in order to spread their good points to the world.
I see. So you are trying to find out what's good about this person.
That's right. That's why I go to Ruff Ruff's shows,
I think it would look better if I let the world know about Ralph Ruff,
or "Her dance and singing are good, so if I pick up on that and express it in the video, maybe it will be conveyed.
If I pick up her dance and song and express them in a video, I think they will be conveyed to the world.
That is my strong point.
That's why I look at the details.
By the way, what did you see when you came to Rough Rough's live performance?
There are no idols that focus on variety and laughter,
You know, there is a song in the middle of a song where they make a big joke?
Yeah, right.
So I thought it would be nice to have a song like that,
I thought it would be nice to have something like that.
Oh, yes, that's right.Oh, yes.
No one does songs like that one on singing shows, right?
That's right.
Finally, I have a question for you,
You have been doing music programs for 16 years,
What is the most important thing for an idol group?
Well, I guess there are various things depending on the stage of the group,
But as an idol star,
When you are around the age of Ruff Ruff, you start to do your own work.
And then, when each of them started to have their own personal jobs,
I felt envious of them,
I think I would like to do personal work too.
Yes, yes.
I probably do.
However, even if I start my own business inside the company, I still don't know anything about it,
But even if you start your own private business internally, the customers you meet from now on don't know anything about it.
That's where you start, right?
That's why it's always a team effort.
I don't envy them,
I think of it as a mentality of "congratulations" rather than envy.
So you want to support the group that is the best.
Yes, that's right.
I want to be at the site where all the members are gathered.
Yes, yes.
I am happy to work individually.
But you are supporting them in order to go to the site where all the members are gathered.
Hmmm...
I see.
I don't want to be alone outside and say, "I'm Ruff Ruff's whatever,
I would like you to introduce yourself.
Ah, yes, that's right.
That's wonderful.
There was a lot of variety,
I've heard so many stories.
I heard so many stories.
How was it, Mr. Sakuma?How was it, Mr. Sakuma?
Variously.
I mean, there's no need to invite geeks here.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I understand.
That's why I never hear the opinions of top water directors,
I'm really valuable.
No, really.
Shimada-kun is an idol geek, though,
But a director who is really successful, you end up falling in love with that person.
I have a feeling that I like him.
It's better to have a feeling of liking, and it's better to make people like you,
But I don't know why I'm doing this project today.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I really don't understand.
I said that too.
I'm also going to be in a music program.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
A music program, too.
That's right. I'm still working on Direkongo, too.
Well then, let's clean up this studio and go home today, shall we?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
We don't know who's watching.
Let's do our usual thing for the last time.
What do you say?
What are you going to say? What do you want to do?
I want to be on FM.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Let's do it.
I want to be in the Styron Festival on FM!
Thank you very much.
Shibana-san, please take care of me.
Um, I'll say it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
So this time it was Shibana-san. Thank you very much.So this time it was Shibasana. Thank you very much.
Look forward to seeing you next time!
Sorry, sorry.
But I just thought of something, and I do all kinds of things.
Definitely.
Follow me!
Yeah, I know, I was just making a statement.
I thought, "No, that's not possible.
I chuckled.
I asked him and he said you were right.
I shouldn't have laughed.
I was like, "I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
I thought for sure I'd get it right.
And then I heard it.
I was right.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I missed your ride.
I'll be so happy when I win.
I'm sure you'll be happy.
It's important that you take the time to answer.
Yay!
If I can write something intense.
I'll feel like I made a mistake.
I thought I'd write something...
I thought I'd write something shocking.
But when I wrote it, everyone was pretty peaceful.
I was the only one
I wrote something radical.
I thought it was supposed to be like that.
I'm glad you did.
You know, your fans are really nice.
I don't have a lot.
I don't have any favorites.There's nothing you like.
There's nothing to like.
It's hard, isn't it?
You've learned a lot.
I learned a lot.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
This time
I'm clumsy, so here's my version.
I'm clumsy.
It's not easy.
Subscribe to my channel
or "press the good button" or something like that.
I'm just trying to be upbeat.
I'm Yent.
I'm a bit of a klutz.
I'm not a very good person.
I'd like you to promote me more.
But I'm so clumsy.
I'm clumsy